Larisa Yushkevich

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

About

I've been interested in web design and programming for over 3 years now. Since then, I've become a skilled Frontend Developer who worked in various industries and with various technologies.

Now my goal is to become a Full Stack Developer by learning the modern back-end stack. I would be happy to add value to your business using both my existing skills and new ones (I am passionate about learning new technologies).

Professional Experience

LeverX Group – Trainee Front-end Developer (SAPUI5)

September 2021 - October 2021, certificate

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SAPUI5, OData, Git

- Mastered JS concepts: lexical environment, scope, closure, HTTP, AJAX, inheritance, async code, promises
- Learned SAPUI5 framework basics: controls, models, data binding, OData protocol, MVC pattern
- Explored ODataModel CRUD operations

BIVIAR Partners – Front-end Developer

October 2021 - present

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SAPUI5, OData, Vue.js, Vuex, Vue Router, Vuetify, Axios, Git

- Developed SPAs with SAPUI5 framework based on MVC architecture (SAP HCM module)
- Developed components for creating complex business management system (CRM, HRM - internal corporate system) using Vue.js, Vuex, Vue Router and various libraries: Vuetify, Axios, Vue-ApexCharts
- Implemented API integration using Axios
- Discussed choices and common sense of using technologies for new project features and their realization
- Refactored 200+ components, making them readable and self-descriptive with Style Guides and best practices

English Level

B1 (Intermediate)

t.me/yushkevichlar

yushkevichlar@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/yushkevichlar

Skills Summary

Languages:

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript

Tools/Other skills:

- Git
- npm
- Figma
- HTTP, REST API
- OOP

Libraries/Frameworks:

- SASS/SCSS
- SAPUI5
- React, Redux, React Router
- Tailwind CSS
- Vue.js 2/3 (Options API, Composition API)
- Vuex, Vue Router
- Vuetify
- Axios

Education

Information Systems and Technologies (in public health)

2018 - 2022

International Sakharov Environmental Institute of Belarusian State University

Additional Education

<u>Udemy - Web developer 2021 course</u>

March 2021 - May 2021, certificate

- Using HTML5 and CSS3 in real projects
- JavaScript and jQuery basics
- · Git, GitHub
- Bootstrap, FlexBox, Grid
- Responsive web design

Projects

Portfolio

Designed and coded my personal website using HTML, CSS and JavaScript. Responsive design, dark/light themes and animations made it dynamic and fascinating.

The new version was made with React and Tailwind CSS.

Weather App

Vanilla JS application developed using OpenWeatherMap API. Shows both Celsius and Fahrenheit degrees, icon that illustrates the weather and short description of current forecast.

Vue Firebase Chat

Realtime Chat application made with Vue 3 (Composition API) and Firebase Realtime Database.



github.com/yushkevichlar



https://yushkevichlar.github.io/Portfolio2